channelpages.com 2015-06-09

# Channel Pages Privacy Policy

## Channel Pages Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, use the Channel Pages service, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

We also collect information from your Google and YouTube accounts once you securely authorize our application via oauth. This information includes your contact information, other demographic information about you, as well a statistics and information about your YouTube channel and it’s viewing audience. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To create and publicly display a profile of your YouTube channel and it’s viewing audience (including, but not limited to channel statistics, audience demographics, and popular topics) 
  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your use of Channel Pages, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please contact us to request removal. 

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless you trigger such action (such as sending a message to another party through Channel Pages). Personally identifiable information does not include your YouTube channel name or various social network identities. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and updating the previously collected information. 

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://channelpages.com/meta/terms/ 

### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 09/12/2013 

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.ChannelPages.com  
150 West 25th Street  
New York, New York 10001  
USA  
hello@channelpages.com 

Close

## Connect Your YouTube Channel

To securely verify your info, please sync your channel’s YouTube account with Channel Pages. 

**Why do we ask for the “Manage Account” permission?**

As a **YouTube Certified Partner** , we are held to the highest security standard required by YouTube, and ask for this permission so that actions you (and only you) take are easy and secure. 

Sync Now
